They say once you learn how to ride a bike, you never forget.
人们说一旦你学会骑自行车，就一辈子都不会忘。
Most of us learnt when we were kids, and many still strap on our helmets, put our feet on the pedals, and shoot off for a ride around the streets.
我们大多数人都是小时候学会骑车的，现在还有不少人会戴上头盔，蹬上脚踏板，骑着车在街道上疾驰。
In recent times, cycling has seen a boost in popularity, so the question is, what makes it so appealing to people to straddle their bikes once again?
近年来，骑行的受欢迎程度大幅提升，那么问题来了，是什么让人们再次热衷于骑上自行车呢？
First, let’s look at the health benefits.
首先我们来看看骑行对健康的益处。
Cycling can improve your cardiovascular health and burn excess body fat.
骑行能够改善心血管健康，燃烧体内多余脂肪。
Strengthening your leg muscles in your calves and thighs helps to increase your potential torque and cadence.
强化小腿和大腿部位的腿部肌肉，有助于提升骑行扭矩和踏频的潜力。
And cycling’s benefits aren’t just physical, but mental as well.
而且骑行带来的好处不止体现在身体上，对心理健康也大有裨益。
A long ride in the countryside could help you to clear your mind, or de-stress.
在乡间长途骑行，可以帮助你理清思绪、释放压力。
But it’s not only about your body and mind – there are also some plus sides for your wallet’s health.
但骑行的好处可不止于身心层面，对钱包来说也是一大福音。
Cycling can be a great way to commute or get about town.
骑行是通勤或在市区出行的绝佳方式。
By cycling, you save money on fuel or train fares.
骑车出行可以省下燃油费或火车票钱。
If you do drive into work, sometimes finding somewhere to park can be a nightmare, whereas finding somewhere to chain your bike up can be much simpler.
如果开车上班，有时候找停车位会是一场噩梦，而找地方锁自行车则要简单得多。
Then, on the train, there are changes at stations and other commuters speaking loudly on their phones to deal with.
坐火车的话，还得应对换乘以及其他通勤者大声打电话的干扰。
Cyclists face neither of these issues.
骑行者则不会遇到这两种麻烦。
And if you’re worried about safety, there are designated cycle lanes in many major cities.
如果你担心安全问题，许多大城市都设有专用自行车道。
Wearing high-visibility clothing, sometimes referred to as ‘hi-vis’, is another way to improve your safety when cycling on the roads.
穿上高能见度服装（有时被称为“反光服”），也是提升道路骑行安全性的另一种方法。
Finally, cycling can also be good for the environment.
最后，骑行对环境也有益处。
It can help you to reduce your carbon footprint.
它能帮助你减少碳足迹。
Not pumping out fumes into the atmosphere is better for the planet and your own environment.
不会向大气中排放尾气，无论是对地球还是对周边环境来说，都是一件好事。
So, whether people want to cycle for their health, getting about town, their wallet, the environment, or a combination of all of them – the popularity of cycling is on the rise.
所以，无论人们是为了健康、出行、省钱、环保，还是兼而有之，骑行的热度都在持续攀升。